[Music]
Oh, I can't believe
But I can't be in this place
This must all be
An illusion skipping frames
Years of living
With a cold and empty space
And it haunts me
Every time I think I'm safe
Do you feel me?
I know I don't
What you have?
Do you feel love, love, love?
Do you feel love?
When you're alone?
Do you feel at home?
Do you feel love, love, love?
Do you feel?
[Music]
Like a frenzy
Like an ocean of a flow
This must all be
Just an oxidative host, oh I'm changing
And I feel more like a ghost
Like a specter
In your headlights or in the road
Do you feel love?
I know I don't
What you have?
Do you feel love, love, love?
Do you feel love?
When you're alone?
Do you feel at home?
Do you feel love, love, love?
Do you feel?
[Music]
So clean you may say that you fool me well
'Cause I've kept my distance, it just made it worse
But I've learned to live with the way that he is
Something you're missing made you who you were
'Cause I've kept my distance, it just made it worse
But now I've learned to live with the way that he is
[Music]